Viewers, receive – in the name of Jesus!
Receive your own portion, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Are you on the sickbed?
Wherever you are and wherever your sickness, disease is located -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Dry bones –rise again!
You, satan, we know your activities, strategies and tactics – we know you!
Leave my people!
In the name of Jesus!
You, demon – leave, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Wherever that affliction – I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, begin to seal your blessings with the blood of Jesus.
Seal it!
Seal your blessings with the blood of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 16/11/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 16/11/2018